

Contact

Date of Birth 28-11-1995

Phone 078 979 3059

Email gm.tranhuuhanh@gmail.com

Address 928 Le Van Luong Street,

Nha Be District, Ho Chi Minh Clty

Education

2014 - 2019

Industrial Automation

Ho Chi Minh City University of Transport

Skills

HTML- CSS

HTML5-CSS3

SASS - SCSS

Javascript, ES6

Boostrap, Tailwind

Git, Github

Call API (Fetch / Axios)

ReactJS (Hook + Redux)

NodeJS (ExpressJS + mongoose)

Resful API

Other Skills

Other languages:

Basic C/C++, TypeScript

Basic Adobe Photoshop

English: TOEIC 500

Hanh Tran

JavaScript Developer Fresher

Profile

I work as the Electrical Engineer from 2019.

I knew about HTML-CSS when i worked a I.O.T project in the University. In 2021, I start to learn about Front end and build my personal projects.

In the school, i leaned many things from my mentor, until now I'm still updating

my knowledge everyday.

Experiences

2015 - 2019 Learn C in Embedded Programming at University.

2021 - 10/2022 Follow the self-study courses (F8, Udemy).

Learn to become a Front-end Developer

CyberSoft Academy.

6/2022 - present Work at GPT GROUP as a Front-end Dev.

Projects

Studious Home Page - Clone

Link deploy: https://hanh28111995.github.io/StudiousHomePage

Source: https://github.com/Hanh28111995/StudiousHomePage.git

Technology: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap

Movie-Cybersoft (Customer page & Admin page)

Link deploy: https://moviebooking-ht.vercel.app

Source: https://github.com/Hanh28111995/bc29_reactjs_capstone_tranhuuhanh.git

Technology: ReactJS, Hook, Redux, React-Router-Dom, Antd, axios,...

Jira - Clone (Customer page & Admin page)

Link deploy: https://bc29-jira-clone-tranhuuhanh.vercel.app

Source: https://github.com/Hanh28111995/BC29_CAPSTON_FINAL_HANH_TRAN.git

Technology: ReactJS, Hook, Redux, React-Router-Dom, Antd, axios, React-Player,...

CyberPhone (...building)

Link deploy: https://nodejs-blog-a4ol.onrender.com/

Source: https://github.com/Hanh28111995/Cyberphone_nodejs.git

Technology: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Mongoose, express-handlebars, MongoDB,...